The Princess Sapphire
Knight of the Ribbon
♪ Atashi no miru yume himitsu nano ♪
The dreams I see are my secret
♪ Dare ni mo iwanai himitsu nano ♪
I won’t tell anyone—it’s my secret
♪ Akai manto hira hira ♪
A red cape fluttering
♪ Uma o tobasu oujo ♪
Galloping on a horse—the princess
♪ Sore ga atashi ♪
That’s me!
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Lula-dula-lula-dula ♪
-
♪ Lulu laa, lulaa ♪
♪ Ribon no kishi wa ♪
The Knight of the Ribbon,
♪ Honto wa hontto wa ♪
Truly, truly,
♪ Atashi nano sa ♪
It’s really me!
Eighth Episode
The Winged Horse
The Phantom Horse
Where am I?
Babies about to be born are being sent down to Earth.
That's it!
This is Heaven!
I must be dreaming of Heaven.
This is me!
Back when I was in Heaven, I was quite a mischievous angel.
God is separating the babies into boys and girls!
There, open wide!
The child who drinks the blue heart becomes a boy, and the child who drinks the red heart becomes a girl!
I stole a blue heart from the basket!
Hey, wouldn't it be better to be a boy?
I don't know which is better.
I'll give you a boy's heart.
Who's next?
You are going to be a girl.
The child who swallows the red heart will become a girl!
I already swallowed the blue heart.
So it's Tink's doing again!
Where is that Tink hiding?
Right there!
I'm sorry.
Apologizing won't fix this!
When that child is born, won't it be impossible to tell if it's a boy or a girl?
Go down to the mortal realm and extract the boy's heart from that child!
Do you understand?
Go!
What, so it was just a dream after all?
Tink!
Be quiet all ready...
Who is it?
Calling me in the middle of the night like this.
It's me.
Pegasus!
Long time no see.
When did you get here? From Heaven.
What did you come here for?
Hey, how is God doing?
Hey, what's wrong? Pegasus...
Tink, did you forget God's orders?
I can no longer rely on you.
I will take Sapphire's boy's heart and return.
Hey, wait up, Pegasus!
There's a reason for this, a reason!
Even I know the reason.
When you're in Heaven, you know everything that happens on Earth.
But God's command is a command.
I'll do this job myself. Tink, I won't ask you anymore.
Hey, don't say that...
Ah, I wonder where Pegasus went?
At times like this, if I had wings like back when I was in Heaven,
I could float softly through the air like the wind...
Being human is so inconvenient...
Oh no, this is a total disaster!
Your Majesty, I have news!
What is it?
It's incredible!
Pegasus... soaring Pegasus is...
What did you say?! Pegasus?!
It took flight...
It flew up into the heavens...
It really is Pegasus.
How wonderful!
Truly magnificent.
Happiness will surely come to Silverland...
Yes, it surely will come, happiness...
Why?
Hey, why does happiness come when Pegasus flies?
That's what people have said since ancient times.
I hope Pegasus stays with us forever.
Yeah, is that so... Ah, Pegasus is going away!
Happiness is slipping away!
Sapphire!
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
Tink, help me.
They say that if you catch Pegasus, happiness will come.
Happiness?
Like I said, Pegasus—there's that kind of legend about him.
I told you, Pegasus didn't bring happiness.
I can't tell you the reason, but it came to make Sapphire more feminine.
Pegasus brings happiness, huh? I've found something good here.
I was sure it was around here, but...
Well, if it isn't here, it isn't here, Sapphire!
Shut up!
Tink, wait right there!
Got it?
Where could Pegasus have hidden?
There it is!
I won't let you get away this time!
Sapphire, you're finally alone.
Ready...
Hey, who did this?
I was so close to catching Pegasus, too.
Strange, I thought it was around here...
Nylon!
Well, well, if it isn't Prince Sapphire.
Have you seen Pegasus?
Pegasus?
Did you say Pegasus?
It is the horse of happiness.
The horse that brings peace to Silverland.
Do you really not know?
No, not at all.
Well, that sounds fine, but if such a horse exists, Silverland would be overjoyed.
Now, if you will excuse me.
Fine, my foot! That little tomboy...
Pegasus is properly loaded in this carriage, you know.
Ah, that's right, I have a good idea. Oh?
My, as expected of Grand Duke Duralumin's trick mansion.
The power of the dynamite given by the Grand Duke is truly something.
This is an extraordinarily splendid horse.
But, does having Pegasus really bring happiness?
Why, yes, yes, of course.
What happiness?
Does happiness bite you on the nose, you fool?
Please wait, Grand Duke Duralumin.
I've thought of something even better. Let me whisper in your ear...
Sapphire is?
Yes, she is frantically chasing after Pegasus.
We can use that to finish off that prince once and for all...
Good! Well, aren't you quite the clever one.
This is all thanks to bringing Pegasus...
Now then, a horse that looks like Pegasus... a horse that looks like Pegasus...
No good, your face is too round.
You've got a mean look in your eyes.
After all, elegance is number one when it comes to being Pegasus.
It must be refined.
Your Grace, it is finished.
How do you like my handiwork?
Splendid, splendid.
Just as expected of Nylon.
And now, put this bee inside the fake Pegasus's ear.
The anesthesia lasts for 10 minutes.
In 10 minutes, the bee will wake up.
And once the bee goes wild, Sapphire will fall from the top of the tower...
I wonder where Pegasus went?
Ah, it's over by that door.
Sapphire! Wait!
That's
Sapphire!
No it's not!!
That's a fake Pegasus!!
I caught you!!
It's about time the fake Pegasus starts going wild, isn't it?!
Come on, fly!!
Try flying!!!
Three, two, one, zero!!
Kaboom!!
Hey!
What's going on?!
Don't thrash around so much!!
This is terrible, this is terrible, this is terrible!
Um, I'm in real trouble... Um, um, what should I do? Hey, hey...Hey, pull yourself together!
Hey, don't thrash around!
Opal!
Whoa, we're gonna fall!
Oh God!
Thank goodness...
Sapphire!
Sapphire, are you okay?
This was the trick.
They were planning to kill Sapphire from the very beginning, I'm sure of it.
Just as I said, it was a fake Pegasus, right?
But who would use a fake Pegasus...?
It's definitely that Nylon guy's doing again.
Ugh, that utterly infuriating Sapphire.
Damn it, just how lucky can that fellow get? Crap!
Nylon!
What are you doing in a place like this?
Well, well, Prince Sapphire, I am taking an afternoon stroll.
Now then, if you will excuse me.
Wait!
Why did you use a fake Pegasus?
Where is the real Pegasus?
What are you talking about?
Your Highness, you seem to be mistaken about something...
Playing dumb won't work!
You're the one who hid Pegasus.
It has to be right here!
If you insist that much, please, go right ahead and search.
That's enough!
But no matter where you hid him, I will definitely find Pegasus!
Opal, do me a favor.
With your sense of smell, you can tell where Pegasus is, right?
Go search for him.
There's no mistake this time.
Leave it to me.
I have already set the second and third schemes in motion.
Using the real Pegasus.
Lord Sapphire.
Who's there?
I am a humble person.
I have come to bring you news.
Up ahead at the rocky mountain, Pegasus has its foot trapped between the rocks.
Trapped in the rocks?
Is that true?
Is Pegasus really there?
All right, I'll go, guide the way!
All right, I have no more use for you!
He's here!
He's coming, he's coming!
Help!
I'm a friend!
You fool!
That isn't Sapphire!
It IS Sapphire!
No!
It's not Sapphire!
It IS Sapphire!
Ready, fire!
Pegasus, I've come to help!
Sapphire!
Tink!
Watch out!
Your Highness, today I shall take your life!
Next is the head!
That was close, Sapphire!
Hey, Pegasus!
Sapphire!
Don't get on Pegasus!
Wait!
Wait! Mr. Pegasus
Tink!
Help!
It's flying towards the mountain border!
Pegasus!
Sapphire!
Tink!
Mr. Pegasus!
You mustn't take Sapphire's boy's heart!
Sapphire wants to keep her boy's heart!
This country has so many bad laws!
Until those can be fixed, please leave Sapphire as she is!
If you insist on taking her boy's heart,
I will protect Sapphire even if I have to fight you!
Once Silverland is at peace, I promise I will take her boy's heart back to heaven myself!
Mr. Pegasus!
You finally understand!
Mr. Pegasus
Give my regards to God in heaven!
Pegasus is
going back to heaven!
Goodbye!
Mr. Pegasus!
Happiness isn't brought by Pegasus—
it's something I create with my own power!
All right, let me do this!
And let me make Silverland an even richer and happier country!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Sen'nen man'nen hyakuman-nen ♪
A thousand years, ten thousand years, a million years,
♪ Ribbon de tsunagou ichioku-nen ♪
Let’s connect with ribbons for a billion years!
♪ Akuma ga kute mo arashi ga kute mo ♪
Even if demons come, even if storms arrive,
♪ tsunaida kokoro wa hanarenai ♪
Our bonded hearts will never part.
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
♪ Tarari Ratta Ritta Ratta Rattattaa ♪
-
♪ Kyahoo! Kyahoo! Kyahoo! ♪
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Subtitled by
SilverlandSubs
tinyurl.com/SilverlandSubs
Opening & Ending Song Lyrics Translation by
Natalia Arlovskaya
lyricstranslate.com/en/
translator/natalia-arlovskaya
EAN-13 : 8-031179-423880
ASIN : ‎ B0DQ54LVY1
EAN-13 : 8-031179-426225
ASIN : ‎ B0F1V5YTQP